Speaker 1: Well, isn't this just interesting?
Speaker 2: Also, totally blew up the use of hydroxychloroquine. And then when it comes to ivermectin,
Speaker 3: which, by the way, because I had close contact by so many people, I referred them to doctors who actually had the courage and compassion to treat vaccine-injured individuals. It works.
But I was going to
Speaker 3: ask
Speaker 2: you whether you were involved in the FDA attack
Speaker 2: on ivermectin you had a
Speaker 3: interview on cnn on august 29th of 2021 where again i just don't want to take time to find the exact quote but you know said there's no evidence there's no evidence
Speaker 4: that ivermectin is helpful on that exact same day and i've got the i've got the studies right here there was a website
Speaker 5: that was tracking
the
Random
Speaker 5: controlled studies. - That's a stack of papers. - So here they are showing 60,
Speaker 6: 70% efficacy of ivermectin. The same thing you say, there's no evidence. There's all kinds of evidence. Loved
ones had to go to
Speaker 8: hospitals, had to sue hospitals. Just, would you try it?
So I would
Speaker 8: wanna know, to what extent were you involved
in
Speaker 8: sabotaging
Speaker 2: hydroxychloroquine, ivermectin and and did you do that because you knew
the only way
Speaker 2: you get emergency use authorization for these drugs
Speaker 9: these experimental gene therapy was if there was no effective treatment you couldn't get the emergency use authorization so is that why you help sabotage
I
Speaker 10: mean you
Speaker 11 (higher-pitched voice): heard it from the horse's mouth right there 70% effectiveness
and i love
Speaker 11 (higher-pitched voice): how fauci just sat there and plead the fifth probably a smart move on you there fauci because you know you know that stuff actually works
and you
Speaker 11 (higher-pitched voice): know that there is beyond that stack
Speaker 12 (higher-pitched voice): that that man was holding of evidence of the efficiency the effectiveness of ivermectin
Speaker 11 (higher-pitched voice): okay
Speaker 11 (higher-pitched voice): And if you would like to get you some ivermectin, you know, just to have around the house, just in case, go to the link in my bio.
Use the code
Speaker 11 (higher-pitched voice): word petty to save you some money, okay? Fauci,
Speaker 12 (higher-pitched voice): honey, the truth will set you free, baby.
Speaker 12 (higher-pitched voice): Quit denying it. After
Speaker 13 (higher-pitched voice): everything that's come out about Fauci, everything that we've learned, they're still wearing masks. You heard me right. Is there any hope for these people? Because I'm questioning if they will ever come out of this TDS, like, psychosis they're in. So today I go to lunch and there's a park outside of the place that we eat and there is this...
Speaker 13 (higher-pitched voice): woman man I don't know what it was wearing a mask in public gets in their car and keeps the mask on and it just got me thinking I was like thinking about it the whole way home is there any hope for these people like after everything that we've learned if you didn't know because before they were like it's all a conspiracy theory none of it's true we need to be safe still so all of the stuff that's come out Anthony Fauci's diary that he didn't want released unless it was
redacted
Speaker 13 (higher-pitched voice): who the F redacts a diary. I mean we literally got to see behind the scenes that Anthony Fauci as we all suspected was just a power hungry little gremlin that no one ever liked and he got a taste of fame and and he ran with it. He made up all this nonsense that he didn't even believe himself so that he could gain power and these people are still wearing masks. Like is it that they just don't want to do any research? They don't want to read anything that's come out? They just want to like be spooked
Speaker 13 (higher-pitched voice): moonfed BS because I cannot imagine living in fear your whole life thinking that you know germs are out to get you and there's this big bad boogeyman and then never wanting to make sure that you're scared for legitimate reasons like how do we move forward in society with these people when they can't even like open up a video and watch it because they've been told that we are evil and we are liars wouldn't you want to make sure that that's true because I sit and watch all your videos all day every day to make
sure
Speaker 13 (higher-pitched voice): that you're still insane, newsflash you are. It is just crazy to me that the Democratic Party has convinced all these people that they just need to isolate themselves, they need to watch all liberal content, and they need to make sure that they're not allowing any different ideas into their head. Because I can guarantee if that person had just done a little bit of research or watched any of the stuff that's come out about Fauci, they wouldn't still be wearing a face diaper.
But
Speaker 13 (higher-pitched voice): I guess, why am I surprised? I shouldn't even be surprised. Do
Speaker 14: you guys think that these people are ever going to wake up? Let me know.
Hunters on the
Speaker 15: warpath, the target, same as the commies. I'm not
running
Speaker 16 (lower-pitched voice): for anything, so I can say whatever the f*** I want. And here's what I think. I think Chuck Schumer is a piece of s***.
Speaker 16 (lower-pitched voice): and that he'd my dad over. Nancy Pelosi at the time also was involved in that. And so I don't have anything nice to say about it right now. We're not friends with Nancy Pelosi. And I'm supposed to be the guy that says, oh, but you know
Speaker 17: what? For what Nancy Pelosi has contributed to this country and to the Democratic Party, I'm not supposed to...
Speaker 19: F*** that, man.
-
Speaker 20: Biden Jr. slashing attacks are drawing blood. Schumer's already wounded, and Hunter's laying the wood to him on Barstool. That's gonna get traction with the young men. The Democrat Party can't afford to lose any more men. More on that
Speaker 21: later. Their generals are being disrespected. The revolution's coming right at 'em.
- Trump has
Speaker 22: turned it into the single most profitable scam of his, please sit down, please sit down.
Speaker 23: - How dare you all talk about corruption?
Speaker 23: How dare you talk about corruption?
Speaker 24: Thank you for your diatribe. Now, let's continue. Let's continue and let the people,
Speaker 25: the people didn't come to hear you. The
Speaker 20: Hamas wing wants Chuck's head on a platter and Hunter's bringing the machete to the fatwa. The party stabbed his dad in the back but left
Speaker 26: the son alive. The mainstream media won't put him on. He's banned. And being banned makes you look dangerous.
Speaker 27: And danger sells. He's a threat to the machine.
Speaker 27: and he's not a communist. He's carving his own
lane. -
Speaker 18: You know who stood with my dad? 100%.
Black
Speaker 16 (lower-pitched voice): Caucus. Hispanic Caucus. The Progressive Caucus.
Speaker 16 (lower-pitched voice): All of the constituent parts of the Democratic Party, which are the base, whether you like it or not.
But you
Speaker 16 (lower-pitched voice): know who didn't stand with him? The editorial board of The New York Times, the Pod Save America guys, you know, David Axelrod, Rahm Emanuel, you know, all of the technocrats of the Democratic Party that don't have any feel or touch for the actual people that actually organize and vote.
Speaker 16 (lower-pitched voice): but they speak for them all the time. So that part did piss me off.
-
Speaker 20: Respect is everything in politics, but when you lose power, you lose respect. So the party's dragging Joe's name through the mud because it cost them.
- People want fighters. I
Speaker 28: think President Biden
Speaker 29: and Kamala Harris lost the last election because nobody believed that they were fighters.
At least
Speaker 29: they believe Trump was a fighter. He'd fight with a fire hydrant just for the fun of it. Hunter
Speaker 15: Biden's a scrappy cat. A source told me a story about him. He was walking with his brother, Bo, on a college campus. Some guy poked his head out of the second story of a fraternity house, started yelling at Hunter, F you, your dad sucks. Bo said, don't do it, Hunter. Next thing you know, Hunter runs to the house, climbs straight up the facade, grabs a kid from his collar, throws him down from the second floor window.
Speaker 15: and
Speaker 26: just pounds them. That happened so fast, no one even knew what happened. And then they went to the bar. The Democrats could use someone with some animal instincts. And as
Speaker 30: it relates to Donald
Speaker 17: Trump, f*** him, f*** his sons, f*** his daughter. I mean it, all of them, the whole family, down to the grandchildren. I hope for the rest of time that I am on this earth, that their names will live in ignominy.
Speaker 27: Damn
it.
Speaker 27: are banking on a bruiser that's not mamala and knee pads never been in the ring with anybody legit
Speaker 26: the party is so weak it's a turnoff a new quinnipiac poll says only 20 percent of men approve of the democratic party it's basically a bachelorette party they're loud a little annoying and spends everybody else's money you can't win an election without
Speaker 15: men sorry to break it to you but we're half the vote
Speaker 15: Kamala, AOC, guys, don't
Speaker 31: go for that. You can't forget about the fellas.
Speaker 32: - If you're a teamster driving a truck out of, you know, up in Lackawanna County in PA,
Speaker 16 (lower-pitched voice): is that, you know,
Speaker 32: you can
Speaker 16 (lower-pitched voice): vote for Joe Biden because you know he's probably just as confused as you are about transgenderism, and he's
Speaker 17: not gonna shove it down your throat, okay? And he's gonna support your union, and he's gonna make it. But really, I think people miss that about that.
-
Speaker 17: This focus on 0.2% of the population is insane to me. Like, leave 'em be, man.
Speaker 33: Like, Jesus Christ, it must be hard enough already. Like, just, like, leave the be.
-
Speaker 34: Hunter wants to throw woke overboard. Pennsylvania is the keystone state.
Speaker 15: It's the key to the Democrat comeback. When Democrats win it, they win the White House. Scranton Joe Jr. gets it. And so does Senator Schreck.
To a
Speaker 35: bunch of people sit around the room and say, how much kind of crazy do we cram into our platform? And now it's like, oh yeah, let's abolish everything.
Speaker 26: - When a child is three years old, you know what their
Speaker 15: favorite thing to do is? Break stuff. They like the sound it makes. They like watching the pieces scatter, hear it shatter. It's fun. It's cause and effect. They're realizing that they have
Speaker 26: the power to break stuff.
Speaker 26: makes them feel good. They like breaking better than building. Communists are at that stage, developmentally. They want to abolish the presidency, the Senate, Pentagon, police, prisons, and of
Speaker 36: course, ICE. - I think that
Speaker 37: ICE should be abolished and that the people at the head of this agency and the people that are shooting people en masse, the ICE agents that are killing people should be prosecuted and held accountable under United States
courts of law.
Let's be
Speaker 36: clear about who we're ascribing criminality to. - Communism's pretty simple. It's just turning everything upside
Speaker 15: down and watching it break. It's a revenge against America. They want
Speaker 39: to arrest the man and open up the prisons.
Speaker 39: Do you like to have criminals out in the open? What
Speaker 40: do I want criminals out in the open? Sure. I'm fine with that because the idea of a criminal is like a little bit funny to me. Let's
Speaker 41: just say somebody who has raped a woman.
Speaker 40: Totally. Would
you
Speaker 41: like them to be out in the street? I
Speaker 42: think my answer is yes, even though that's a challenging answer to say.
When Joe Schmo
Speaker 43: comes out of prison after serving his rape sentence, commie Chris Robby Blind wants
Speaker 44: to hand him a paycheck for his hard work.
In
Speaker 45: Pennsylvania, they earn 19 cents an hour for the same work folks do outside. And how are victims going to get their restitution from incarcerated folks if those
folks on the
Speaker 46: inside who's supposed to pay them back are getting 19 cents an hour? This
Speaker 47: is what the Obama-Biden party has come to. They
Speaker 26: lost the men and are trying to win them back. Not really. They're replacing them with migrants and communists.
Let me
Speaker 48 (lower-pitched voice): tell you, labels, of course, are being thrown around on both sides. I look for progressive values that I have supported over the years and continue to. There are some who are more aggressive than others. Progressives are joining us in this effort, and we need them. He
said
Speaker 47: it. They need them. They'll take anything or
Speaker 26: anyone. You know people like that. No standards.
Speaker 26: People with no standards have no self-respect, and they get walked all over. That's what we're watching. Now, the only way to get respect is to earn it. I
want your
Speaker 49: viewers to say how much I love to watch Israel eliminating the Hamas leadership. I know that upsets a lot of your viewers and a lot of your founders, but I think it's a great thing. The question is, where does your trash outlet come from
and who's funded
Speaker 49: And now you're sticking a
Speaker 51: microphone in my face. It's not in your face. Are you okay with Prime Minister Netanyahu being
in the United States?
Speaker 51: I'm
Speaker 52: looking. I just love killing Hamas' leadership.
Say
Speaker 26: what you want about Fetterman, but he has strong principles, and he sticks to them. You can disagree with how he feels about Israel, but you always know where he stands. And you respect it. The man's not a weasel. That's why he's a big threat to the left. He's the only one holding the line. That's why they want to put his head on a stake.
But
Speaker 26: Big John's been laughing it off and
Speaker 47: going on
Speaker 35: offense. If someone is frustrated in the Democratic Party, I would be frustrated with someone like Bernie Sanders. Really? Bernie, you have no regret endorsing and proud to stand with an accused rapist, a guy that roughs up his ex-girlfriends, a guy that had a Nazi tattoo on his chest. Some of the things that are outrageous as
a
Speaker 53: Democrat are coming from people in this party, and it's not me.
Speaker 53: For far
Speaker 15: too long, Democrats tiptoed around Bernie Sanders and then had the superdelegates just kneecap him in the dark. Sooner or later, the Democrats are going to have to have this fight under the bright
Speaker 26: lights. And Bernie, he wants that smoke. I would
not put
Speaker 54: too much credibility in what somebody like Feterman says. He
Speaker 55: said you should sit this out. That's not
Speaker 54: what he said? Yeah. Do you think I should take his advice? I probably won't. John, I'm not going to take your advice.
- Think
Speaker 15: about it. This is Vermont versus Pennsylvania. Which state do the Democrats want to side with? Now, Fetterman's from Braddock, a run-down town that saw all its factory jobs move to China. That's a base the party needs if they want to win. But the Bernie bros and the commies, that's not their cup of tea. They're a bunch of wackos with grad degrees. They spend all their money
Speaker 56: on Grubhub. They're lazy and they're entitled.
Speaker 56: people are like, oh yeah,
Speaker 57: well I'm supposed to have that. Well, I deserve that. Well, why don't we have that? Don't we have that? Shouldn't we have that? Who gets that? And then it's like,
Speaker 58: oh okay, well that's the democratic
Speaker 26: socialism. - That's a bad attitude, Bush. You don't deserve anything. You're not entitled to
Speaker 56: anything you don't work for. Oprah, my girl, has had it with this crowd.
You
Speaker 60: ain't having no work-life balance at 22? That's tearing us up, by the way. We're
Speaker 61: all trying to look for the balance. It ain't fair. No,
Speaker 60: no, no, no, no. It ain't fair. It's tearing us up. It's not there. It's not there. You're not supposed to have it. Thank you, though. You're supposed to lay it in, lay
Speaker 62: in the work. Dana
Lash,
Speaker 63: nationally syndicated radio
Speaker 64: host. I can't believe Oprah's right. I mean, you have to grind when you're young. You can't just whine with your hand out.
Speaker 65: I...
Speaker 65: I'm shocked that she said this, although she does have a history of working hard. I mean, she's a capitalist, and that's what really cracks me up, Jesse, about all these leftists. They're really capitalists, but that advice is not wrong. Can I just say something about John Fetterman really quickly, because you had some amazing soundbites about John Fetterman. If Democrats were smart, which we all know
Speaker 66: that they're not, they would put Fetterman out there
Speaker 67 (higher-pitched voice): front and center immediately.
on
Speaker 67 (higher-pitched voice): pretty much everything. That would be, that would create an existential crisis for the GOP right now. But again, they're not smart, so they're not going to put them out there for everything. So go ahead and let the Ariana Presleys, the Rashida Tlaibs, the Ilhan Omar's, the Zoray Mamdani's, go ahead and let them run with the party's messaging. That's just going to be the epitaph as they are burying themselves electorally. I like the
Speaker 68: fight. I like the fact that Bernie
Speaker 15: and Fetterman are going at it. This is the fight the Democrats have tried to
keep a lid on for
Speaker 15: what,
Speaker 69: three elections? If they want to move forward, they have to rumble and we all have to see it. Yeah. Yeah.
They have this
Speaker 66: generational fight right now. You have all of the up and comers that like the idea of what Bernie Sanders is selling, although it doesn't, it's not practical. It doesn't actually work in meat space. It's just sounds good online. And then you have the more practical, you
Speaker 65: know, kind of Fetterman, dare I say, Andy Beshear. I don't want to give them anything, maybe even kind of a Josh Shapiro
Speaker 65: he's not as crazy as the rest of them but you're having this generational fight it's like the kids who've like the people who've never really like they haven't lived enough and they just think that these sound bites and bumper stickers are good and that it means something but it doesn't so they're trying i mean they're having this fight i'm gonna watch it i hope the republicans don't follow suit but you know it's really fun to watch it's just one works in
Speaker 70: meat space and the other doesn't one's an online
phenomenon
We're
Speaker 71: coming over the top!
Speaker 72: This
Speaker 73: chart right here is the reason why it feels like the entire world
Speaker 73: has been mobilized to try to destroy Donald Trump and the MAGA movement. This chart right here is why they hate the man with every fiber of their being. It has nothing to do with his bluster, the way he communicates, how fat he is, the color of his skin, the color of his hair. It has nothing to do with any of that. It doesn't have anything to do with the Epstein files or anything else. It's this chart right here.
-
Speaker 73: Before Donald Trump came down the golden escalators in 2015, the globalists and internationalists were well on their way to dismantling the entire Western civilization. They were well on their way to totally destroying the cultural hegemony of the United States. Americanism was almost dead. And then Donald Trump came down the escalator and he made the pillar of his entire presidency,
Speaker 73: Immigration, building a wall, stopping this from happening. As we now watch countries like Spain's border collapse and thousands and thousands of military-age men flood into the country in one day and their leadership doing nothing to stop it, it is becoming crystal clear that this is the reason why they hate Donald Trump so much. This chart shows you
Speaker 73: What they planned all throughout the Biden administration and executed, and what Donald Trump stopped. This is the reason why it feels like all the forces of internationalism, of globalism, the politics of confiscation, the media, the Democrat Party, the EU, the United Nations, all of them, this right here is why they hate the man, and this is why they have to destroy the man.
Speaker 73: He's the
Speaker 74: only one who was willing to stand up and put a stop to that. The destruction of Western civilization. You support
Speaker 75: this? Yeah, absolutely. An illegal alien being arrested and
Woman 76: detained? Absolutely, yeah. You support the glorification of it? Yes. Why? I believe
Speaker 77 (higher-pitched voice): illegal aliens should be detained and arrested and deported. Okay, you don't believe they as humans deserve some sort of due process? They get due
Speaker 78: process.
-
Speaker 78: Who? - The illegal aliens in that video being detained, arrested. - They were not given due process. They were arrested and
Speaker 77 (higher-pitched voice): taken. Many of them were killed. Americans are being killed by ICE. - Okay. How many Americans have been killed by illegal
Woman 76: aliens? - How many have you seen? 'Cause I know you've seen it. - I have a list. I have a list of 1,600 names just on this list that Ali Pak has put together. - Why do you think it's okay for them to dehumanize them and demonize them throughout social media? - So that's a funny question. Are you still beating your boyfriend? - Excuse
me?
I'm not
Woman 76: beating my boyfriend. - So you're putting me into a box, number one, where they are dehumanizing them, they're not. Being arrested for breaking a federal immigration law is due process, that's not dehumanization. - Did Trump not call them animals? Is that not dehumanization? - Some of them are animals, like MS-13 gang members, yes. - Tackling and ganging up on these immigrants.
Woman 76: Well, they're not immigrants, they're illegal aliens and they broke a law. I will
Speaker 80: get to you
Woman 76: next, okay?
Speaker 81: White girl? I'll get to you next.
Speaker 80: No, we're talking right here. We're not phoning a friend here. We're not
Speaker 75: phoning a friend. We're together,
so...
Speaker 75: Alright, we can do two against one. That's fine. Okay, we'll do two against one. If
Speaker 82: this video doesn't make you pro ice, nothing will.
Within
Speaker 84: minutes of the migrants breaching Spain today, they already started attacking people in the streets. Notice something about this crowd as well. Just look at these people. What do you notice? I noticed one thing specifically right off the bat. I don't see any women and children. I don't see any families. I see military-aged men that are fired up, ready to go, look aggressive. They're so excited to be taking over another country,
they're excited about it.
Speaker 84: about this. It means they're going to be excited when they come across you and you get in their way. And what people don't understand about ICE and about Trump and what he's doing is he's trying to prevent this. You hear the leftist socialists saying they don't want prisons anymore. They don't want ICE anymore. What else could radicalize you for Trump, for ICE? And seeing this happen in Spain where their leader decided to give everyone amnesty and this country is done. Prayers for Spain. Actually, you guys need to pray for Spain. Abolish ICE. You guys better start thinking about voting
Speaker 85: against the DSA, like your life
and your
Speaker 85: country depend on it.
Speaker 86: Thousands upon
Speaker 87: thousands upon thousands upon thousands storming what they call the EU border. Some of them swam to this island. I'm looking at tons of photos, not a single one being a woman. Now the Spanish president Pedro Sanchez said on X that Spain is fully committed to providing an immediate response.
Speaker 87: the situation. I don't know if I believe that. Didn't he refuse to send in the military? I mean, that's what he's being accused of. I mean, it's so similar to Lampedusa, which was a 12 square mile island. It's so similar to what happened in September of 23. Here's another video. Look how many women you don't see. All military age men. Interesting that. All men coming in. All men, not a single woman. Do you see any babies? I didn't see any babies. None, I didn't see any.
Speaker 87: So weird that, hmm,
so all of
Speaker 87: these people coming in,
he said
Speaker 87: they're going to provide an immediate response. They're mobilizing all necessary resources. This is
the time to
Speaker 87: build solutions and a bunch of BS that I don't care about. So I'm curious.
You realize
Speaker 87: that Morocco is pretty much 99 to 100% Muslim.
That's an
Speaker 87: invasion. Yeah.
Speaker 87: What you just saw, that's an act of war. It's an invasion. You have all of these people coming in, military-aged males. That is absolutely an invasion. There's no other way to put it.
Islam
Speaker 88: is not compatible with Western civilization. I don't think it's compatible with the Constitution. It seeks to infiltrate and then dominate and control.
And
Speaker 88: it seems like it's happening. There's mosques going up all over the place. There's churches that have been around for over 100 years. They're being set on fire in New York City and other states, mostly blue states. And it doesn't seem like the radicals are going anywhere. It seems like it's only getting worse. So what do you believe is the actual practical application or practical process to try to minimize that threat?
To be honest with
Speaker 89 (higher-pitched voice): you, we're going to have to coalesce as a culture, which means...
The
Speaker 89 (higher-pitched voice): Christian's got to get along with the non-Christian. The atheist has
Speaker 90: got to get along with the Christian and the Catholic. For that matter, Mormons love America. We've got to band together under this banner, citizens of America.
Speaker 90: It doesn't matter what your flavor is, but if you're an American, you're going to have to stand up and say, listen, Islam is no longer advancing in our cities. That's where you got to do it, David. You got to take it on at the city level. No more permits to build mosques because your theology
Speaker 89 (higher-pitched voice): is diametrically opposed to the U.S. Constitution. You believe in Sharia law.
Speaker 89 (higher-pitched voice): sharia islamic juror jurisprudence is diametrically opposed to the judeo-christian constitution and the government of this nation look what's happened to europe they are so compromised now that they can't even participate in their own national defense because they're afraid of retaliation by the muslims in their cities and in their streets uh
Speaker 89 (higher-pitched voice): Look, it's happening so
Speaker 90: quick now in America, David, that we better we better band together if we love our freedoms. I don't care if you're an atheist. I will stand with you side by side to defend our freedoms that have been blood bought, given to us by God in this wonderful republic, because Islam is against this Republican form of
Speaker 91: government. So
the
Speaker 92: book of James says that even the demons believe demons, they're aware of Jesus' claim to be Lord. They agree that Jesus is Lord,
and unless you
Speaker 92: have this third aspect of faith you do not have a saving faith theologians do this a lot in church history where they'll define what saving faith is historically theologians have said that there are three aspects of saving faith and that for someone to have what theologians refer to as a salvific faith man really all three
Speaker 92: have to be present. The Latin words are noticia, ascensis, and fiducia. This is like super helpful. All right, so noticia, it just means knowledge. So this is your awareness of a fact. You know, Lake Point Church is in Dallas, Texas. That's a fact, awareness of a claim. Okay, ascensis is assent. I'm not just aware of that claim. I agree that that claim is true. And then theologians say there's a third aspect of faith. And unless you have this third aspect of faith,
you
Speaker 92: do not have a saving faith. And the third aspect of faith is fiducia, and it just means trust, okay? So now think about what you got. You got noticia, I am aware of a fact, a census, I agree with a fact, fiducia, I place the entire weight of my life on that fact. I trust that fact, okay? What's interesting is if you read your New Testament, you're going to notice that there are all three categories of people. All right, so for instance, you got Judas had noticia, he was aware of Jesus' claim to be.
Speaker 92: he did not have assent or trust. Judas never affirms the Lordship of Jesus. In fact, he strikingly goes out of his way to avoid affirming the Lordship of Jesus. So he had noticia, but not a census or fiducia. Honestly, the example of someone who has knowledge and assent, but not trust, demons. - Yes. - So the book of James says that even the demons believe and they- - Shudder. - They shudder. So demons, they're aware of Jesus claimed to be Lord.
Speaker 92: number two they agree that jesus is lord but they do not have fiduciary they don't place their the weight of their trust in that okay and then the example of saving faith noticia a census fiducia is peter or any converted person and that's somebody who says this i know that you say your lord i agree that you are lord and i will follow you unto my death because i trust that my lord "God can save me and raise me from the dead." That is saving faith.
Speaker 92: Now, we'll just say this, dude, being a pastor in the Bible Belt, you got a ton of people who they have knowledge and they even have agreement. But very frankly, they do not live their lives in obedience because they do not trust the lordship of Jesus. And to that, I would just give a warning. Two-thirds faith will send you to hell. That's
Speaker 93: a very important thing to be
Speaker 92: aware of.